Man, patrol duty sucks.
Yeah. And it's not like anyone's
gonna cause trouble
this close to the demon king.
If anyone's that stupid, I could take
'em down with just a finger.
Wh-Who are you?!
This is the demon king's...
Rawr!
THE MONSTERS OF TERROR LOOK TOO UGLY!!
"The Monsters of Terror Look Too Ugly!!"
Lady Doux went into the forest all alone?!
B-But that's dangerous!
We must bring her back at once!
It's not unusual for her
to go on walks by herself.
Why are you so panicked?
There was a report from my
subordinates who were on patrol.
The Monsters of Terror, Gauche
and Urun, have appeared.
What? But they're...
Yes. There were once ancient
monsters called "gorgons"
who petrified those
who looked into their eyes.
They are descendants of gorgons.
Those who look into their
eyes freeze in fear
and become unable to move
as though they were petrified.
And they're in the forest?
Jahi.
Yes, Your Majesty! Lady Doux!
I'm on my way!
Huh?
Hmm... Doux's not scary?
Is something wrong?
Look at this, Little Bro.
This little shrimp's so petrified
she can't even speak.
LITTLE BROTHER GAUCHE
BIG BROTHER URUN
Looks like we're on a roll, Big Bro.
Heck yeah! It don't matter
if they're demons or humans!
There ain't nobody who's not
terrified of how ugly we are!
But it ain't no fun if they're just quiet.
If you're gonna be scared, at least
be a bit more dramatic about it.
Scary!
Hey, hey! How do you do
that thing you did?!
Doux wants to be scary, too!
Th-Th-This little shrimp's
got a few screws loose!
She's happy about being scared!
L-Let's get outta here, Big Bro!
Tell me!
Let go of me!
Big Bro!
Doux wants to be scary, too!
Huh? What are you—
What a cute little creature.
Big Bro's been brainwashed?!
Hup!
Look, Little Bro!
This little shrimp's taken a liking
to us even though we're ugly.
You've got lots of eyes!
Y-You're not gonna fool me!
Y-Y-You can't fool me like my Big Bro!
C-C-C-C-Come at me!
I'll make you regret it!
Wait, wait!
"THE FRIENDSHIP WALTZ"
LYRICS: KANATA NAKAMURA
COMPOSITION AND ARRANGEMENT: TAKERU TAKEMIYA
SONG: DOUX, URUN, GAUCHE
Scary, scary
So fun, so fun
Doux's name is Doux
Yup, yup.
It's nice to meet you.
Yeah!
Runtatta, runtatta
The friendship waltz
Let's play together forever and ever
Lookee, lookee!
Are you okay?
I know!
Hup... I'll get you some water!
Doux has so much energy.
They do say that a child has endless
energy when they're playing.
When was the last time
we played with someone like this?
I wouldn't mind playing with Doux forever.
But we'd probably cause her trouble
if we were with her forever.
Yeah.
Not to mention, once she grows up,
she'll see how ugly we
are and be scared of us.
It's best that we're just alone.
Because of that... we should
probably bow out now, Little Bro.
You're right. More importantly,
what's Doux doing?
Doux is practicing scary faces! Rawr!
Oh, yeah. You mentioned that
you wanted to be scary.
Why do you wanna be scary?
Doux wants to be a full-fledged demon.
But I'm not really good at doing bad
things, so Big Sister Jahi said...
No matter what trials I give her,
there's been no change in Lady Doux.
If she'd at least try
to look or act scary...
she might actually change.
So I've been trying to make my face scary.
But Doux isn't very good at that either.
Everyone's got something they can't do.
I've got tons.
Just keep practicing so that
you'll be able to pull it off someday.
Then who knows?
Maybe it'll actually happen.
Okay! I will!
Who would've thought a little kid
would be so worried about something?
Right, Little Bro?
I'm actually really
worried right now, too.
What?! Little Bro?!
I realized something when
we were playing with Doux.
It's been fun being with
just you, Big Bro,
but it's even more fun with
the three of us together!
So that means it'd be even more
fun if we were with even more people.
Gauche, you...
Okay. Then let's go play with everyone!
There's lots of humans and
demons who live in the castle.
If we all play together,
it'll be even more fun!
W-We can't do that.
Everyone'll just be scared of us.
Huh?
Because we're so hard to look at.
You're easy to look at though.
Huh?
Well, look how big you are,
Big Brother Gauche!
You'd be easy to find
if we played hide-and-seek!
Doux?
Oh.
Hard to look at...
HARD TO LOOK AT
HARD TO SEE
EASY TO SEE
Easy to see?
True. There ain't anyone
easier to see than him.
You got us there!
B-Big Bro.
Let's just go, Little Bro.
Don't worry. If we scare 'em,
we'll worry about it then.
Your big bro's got your back.
Big Bro... Doux...
Yeah... you're right!
Save us!
So scary!
Mr. Urun! Mr. Gauche!
We got to be scary!
Yup, yup. You guys were pretty scary.
Right, Big Bro?
Okay, how about... this next?!
Yeah!
Like this, Mr. Urun?!
Yeah. Very good, very good!
Okay, I'll do the next one.
One more time!
Look, Jahi!
Not only was she not in any danger,
but she even befriended
the Monsters of Terror!
Perhaps Lady Doux is already
amazing just as she is.
Thunder, eh?
Thunder... Oh, that reminds me.
Did you hear that on stormy nights
with thunder and lightning,
a wailing ghost appears?
Seriously?!
We've already got Monsters of Terror.
Why'd something like that appear, too?
Hmph. How stupid.
Something's definitely wailing, all right!
C-C-Calm down. Who's scared of any ghost?
I'll make them regret it!
Big Sister Jahi!
Huh?
Lady Doux. Is the thunder...
Goodness. What a fussy little ghost.
Honestly.
You're completely fine with the Monsters
of Terror but scared of thunder.
I guess you really are still just a child.
Goodnight.
THE SPIRIT TOWER IS JUST TOO EXCITING!!
"The Spirit Tower Is Just Too Exciting!!"
So, Jahi, how are Doux's trials going?
I'm terribly sorry.
Because I'm so inadequate...
When you're stuck,
there's always another path.
Your Majesty?
Jahi, I hereby give you a new mission.
A new mission?
This is a very important mission
that I cannot trust to any other.
This will be beneficial as you
continue to give Doux her trials.
You honor me, Your Majesty.
I, Jahi, will see this mission through
even at the cost of my own life.
Papa! I put this on all by myself!
Well done, Doux!
Look. If you just fix
this part, it's perfect!
Yay!
It looks wonderful on... wait!
I came here because you said
this mission was important,
but this is just a vacation!
Don't be so naïve, Jahi!
This is the Spirit Tower.
The Spirit Tower?
Yes.
It's a giant ryokan that lies in the
middle of dimensions where not only demons
but beings from various
worlds come to visit.
Other worlds...
Is there any danger like the pishacha
that once controlled Salamandra?
But of course.
Quarrels at the Spirit
Tower are forbidden.
Meaning this is the perfect place to
find out more about all of the people
we will eventually conquer.
I see. So our true motive
is reconnaissance.
Ah, very good, Doux.
Let's see, here. Papa will join in, too.
Oh, how fun this is!
Papa! Everyone's watching real hard!
Jahi.
Today, we will act as a visiting
family and have tons of fun!
Tons of fun!
Er, Jahi? Where'd you go?
Where'd you go?
This family is hopeless...
No... I need to pull myself together.
First, I will investigate the
patrons from the demon world.
Dance with us, Jahi!
Dance!
What's this?
Is something fun going on?
I wanna see!
Y-Your Majesty! Lady Doux!
Take care of Doux!
Understood! Lady Doux!
I'm heading to you now!
Lady Doux! Lady Doux!
Lady Doux!
Lady Doux! Are you hurt?
Papa and Big Sister Jahi are gone.
What do they look like?
Papa...
Oh!
You dropped this!
Missy?!
Oh, thank goodness. Thank you so much!
You're welcome!
Now, I've gotta thank you.
Do you have anything you wish for?
Let's see... Papa and Big Sister Jahi...
Ah! He's all shaky!
Huh? Wait! I still haven't thanked you!
You're a huge help.
Yay!
Pain, pain, fly away!
My bad back's better in an instant!
Thank you so much!
Mom, I wanna eat that!
I need to pee!
Wait a minute! How long is my husband
going to take in the bathroom?!
I'll help you!
Huh?
Oh my. Look at you, in a good
mood because Doux played with you.
Thank you so much, Doux.
You really helped me out. See you later.
Bye-bye!
There you are!
Lady Doux!
Big Sister Jahi!
Where have you been, Lady Doux?!
And you've been doing
kind things everywhere!
At this rate, you'll never be
a full-fledged demon... huh?
L-Lady Doux?
Um... a lot of people showed up,
and then you and Papa were gone.
I kept wanting to
ask people where you went,
but they were all in trouble...
so I was helping them and...
A-All right. Please calm down!
First of all... I'm just
glad you're safe, Lady Doux.
Let's go find His Majesty.
Make sure you hold onto my hand
this time so we don't lose you.
'Kay!
What's the meaning of this, Your Majesty?
Well, I happened to get along
with this group of guests.
Eat and drink as much as you'd like!
Cheers!
The food here is exquisite!
Doux, let me make your plate for you.
'Kay!
Hup, hup, huppity hup!
Yay! You're amazing, Papa!
Hey there, hottie. Come over
here and have a drink with me.
Don't try to get ahead, you pervy kappa!
What?! Who're you callin' bald?!
I never said that!
You're always callin' me bald!
I'm not bald! I just
have a plate on my head!
Wow! You're so good, Big Sister!
This is how you do it, Lady Doux.
Like this?
Yes. Make sure they don't cross.
I did it! I did it!
I'll share some with you, too, Big Sister!
Thank you.
This food is so squishy and fun.
I wonder what it tastes like.
The water feels great.
I'm being warmed up to my core.
Wait! We're just enjoying
ourselves after all!
Welcome back!
How was it, Jahi?
Did you enjoy your bath?
Yes.
I forgot my mission and acted
disgracefully. I'm so ashamed.
Mission?
Oh, don't worry about that!
That comes second!
What?!
I figured you wouldn't tag
along unless I said that.
Initially, I was planning for this to
be a family trip for just Doux and I,
but she insisted that
you come along as well.
B-But why me?
That's because you're my
big sister, Big Sister Jahi.
Lady Doux...
Well, there you have it!
You get to also enjoy
yourself on our family trip!
Your Majesty... You're becoming
more and more like Lady Doux.
What?! I am?!
You shouldn't be so happy about that.
Ooh. It looks like it's started...
The Spirit Tower's famous
fireworks display.
Big Sister, come sit with me!
No, I...
Isn't this fun?
Yes.
Well, it's not so bad.
THE DEMON KING'S ATTENDANT THINKS TOO MUCH!!
"The Demon King's Attendant
Thinks Too Much!!"
There we go.
I thought about this at the hot springs,
but having long hair just gets in the way.
Now...
Ooh, changing up your look?
Did you fall in love?
Did you fall for an ogre since
you're a meathead attendant?
Or maybe a cyclops is more your type?
There'd be nothing more shameful than if
she were to accuse me of such non-truths!
I know! I'll just cut it short!
That's not a proper hairstyle
for my attendant!
If he says that, I won't
be able to take it back!
Should I tie up?
Or cut it short?
Tie it up?
Cut it short?
Tie? Short? Tie? Short?
Look at that lame hair!
You're fired!
Big Sister...
Is something wrong, Jahi?
No, it's nothing.
In the end, she just
kept her hair as it was!